George Gaylord Simpson Papers 1918-1984 Mss.Ms.Coll.31
American Philosophical Society
- George Gaylord Simpson Papers
  - Series I. Correspondence, 1925-1984; 36 linear feet (Box 1-73)
    - Bogert, Charles M., 1942, 49-50, 62, 79 (Box 9)
    - Bohlag, Larry, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Bohle, Dee, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Bohlin, Berger, 1938, 57, 67 (Box 9)
    - Bohrn, Marie, 1947 (Box 9)
    - Boire, Dorothy, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Bokac, Karen, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Boletin Linotipico (journal), 1939 (Box 9)
    - Bollas, Lawrence M., 1967, 69, 74-77, 79, 81-82 (Box 9)
    - Bombin, Miguel, 1980 (Box 9)
    - Bonaparte, Jose F., 1957, 72-84 (Box 9)
    - Bonaventure, Mother, 1964 (Box 9)
    - Bond, Richard M., 1943 (Box 9)
    - Bondurant, Jack, 1946 (Box 9)
    - Bone, Quentin, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Bonetti, Paolo, 1957-59, 61-62, 64 (Box 9)
    - Bonham-Carter, Graeme, 1972 (Box 9)
    - Bonner, John C., 1966 (Box 9)
    - Bonovitz, Sheldon M., 1973 (Box 9)
    - Bontrager, O.R., 1967 (Box 9)
    - Boodberg, Peter A., 1937 (Box 9)
    - Book Mailer, The, 1960 (Box 9)
    - Booth, Christopher J., 1983 (Box 9)
    - Bordas, Alejandro F., 1932-1955; 50.0 Item(s) (Box 9)
      Biographical and personal data; Evolution -- Plants; Museo Nacional de Historia Natural, Buenos Aires; Paleontology; Political issues -- Argentina; Publication; Requests for aid in finding positions; Scientific organizations, meetings, programs; World War II -- Impact on science
    - Borden, Gavin, 1975 (Box 9)
    - Bordes, Francois, 1946 (Box 9)
    - Borgmeier, Thomas, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Boring, Edwin G., 1956-59, 66 (Box 9)
    - Borntraeger, Gebruder, 1931 (Box 9)
    - Borrissiak, A., 1934-35 (Box 9)
    - Borsari, Alan, 1963 (Box 9)
    - Boston College, 1967 (Box 9)
    - Boston University, 1963, 71 (Box 9)
    - Boswall, Jeffery, 1981 (Box 9)
    - Boucot, Arthur J., 1972-1982; 2 folders (Box 9)
      Bibliographical matters; Biographical and personal data; Editorial matters; Educational matters; Evolution; Evolution -- Reptiles; Gould, Stephen Jay; Lectures, public speaking; Paleoscatology; Political issues -- Environment; Publication -- Attending Marvels; Research support; Reviews; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; World War II -- Impact on science; Zoology; Zoology -- Animal behavior
    - Bourliere, F., 1951, 54 (Box 9)
    - Bowdoin College, 1953-55 (Box 9)
      Rates of evolution
    - Bowersock, G.W., 1970 (Box 9)
    - Bowker, Albert H., 1959 (Box 9)
    - Bowling Green State University, 1959-60 (Box 9)
      Science and Mathematics Symposium, 28 Feb., 1960
    - Bown, Ralph, 1956 (Box 9)
      Bell System Science Series (TV)
    - Bown, Thomas, 1971, 75, 79, 83 (Box 9)
    - Boxer, Sarah, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Boyd Printing Co., 1974 (Box 9)
    - Boyd, Donald W., 1974 (Box 9)
    - Boyd, Julian P., 1958 (Box 9)
      Thomas Jefferson and fossils
    - Boyden, Alan A., 1936,44, 47-48, 50-53, 59, 60, 66, 72-73 (Box 9)
    - Boylan, Grace, 1965 (Box 9)
    - Boyle, W.S., 1950 (Box 9)
    - Brace, C. Loring, 1969, 73-74 (Box 10)
      Cuvier
    - Bradley, William C., 1966-67 (Box 10)
    - Bradley, Wilmot H., 1940, 68 (Box 10)
    - Braestrup, F.W., 1954, 63 (Box 10)
    - Brailovsky, Harry, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Bram, Leon L., 1971 (Box 10)
    - Brameld, Theodore, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Brandt, A.E., 1940-41 (Box 10)
    - Brandwein, Paul F., 1958 (Box 10)
    - Branner, George C., 1932 (Box 10)
    - Branstrater, Jon W., n.d. (Box 10)
    - Brattle Inn, 1947 (Box 10)
    - Brattstrom, Bayard H., 1980 (Box 10)
    - Brauner, Florence, 1970-72 (Box 10)
    - Braybrooke, Neville, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Brazil and Argentina Trip - Official Correspondence, 1954-55 (Box 10)
    - Bremer, John, 1961-62 (Box 10)
      Harcourt, Brace, and World, Inc.
    - Brentano's Book Store, Inc., 1936-37, 65 (Box 10)
    - Brereton, J. LeGay, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Bretting, Peter, 1978 (Box 10)
      Allometry
    - Brewer, Herbert, 1954-55 (Box 10)
    - Brief, Kay, 1983 (Box 10)
    - Brien, Paul, 1946 (Box 10)
    - Briggs, Richard I., 1963 (Box 10)
    - Brigham Young University, 1958 (Box 10)
    - Brigham, Edward M., 1924 (Box 10)
      Triassic beds, House Creek Canyon
    - Brightfield, L.O., 1964 (Box 10)
    - Brighton, A.G., 1947 (Box 10)
    - Brilliande, Robert, 1966 (Box 10)
    - Brinton, Crane, 1962 (Box 10)
    - Brisbin, W.C., 1978 (Box 10)
    - Bristol Hotel, 1972 (Box 10)
    - British Association for the Advancement of Science, 1951 (Box 10)
    - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1957, 1966 (Box 10)
    - British Columbia, University of (Department of Geology and Geography), 1926 (Box 10)
    - British Council, 1978 (Box 10)
    - British Museum (Natural History), 1926, 1951 (Box 10)
    - Broadbooks, H.E., 1970 (Box 10)
    - Brock, Jerome A., 1954 (Box 10)
    - Brockhaus, F.A., 1926 (Box 10)
    - Brodkorb, Pierce, 1959, 69, 73-74, 77-79 (Box 10)
    - Broek, L.J.H. van den, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Broili, F., 1937 (Box 10)
      Tritylodon
    - Brongersma, L.D., 1946 (Box 10)
    - Bronk, Detlev W., 1940 (Box 10)
    - Bronson, Wilfrid Swancourt, 1941-42 (Box 10)
    - Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1947-48 (Box 10)
    - Brookhaven Symposium on Biology, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Brookline, Public Schools of, 1965 (Box 10)
    - Brooklyn College, 1952, 54 (Box 10)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences, 1950 (Box 10)
    - Brooks, Charles F., 1937-38 (Box 10)
    - Brooks, J.C., 1954 (Box 10)
    - Brooks, Peggy, 1969 (Box 10)
    - Broom, Robert, 1933-34 (Box 10)
    - Brower, Anne, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Brown University, 1960 (Box 10)
    - Brown and Williamson Tobacco Corp., 1945 (Box 10)
    - Brown, Alastair, 1941-42 (Box 10)
    - Brown, Barnum, 1925-27, 63 (Box 10)
    - Brown, F. Martin, 1961 (Box 10)
    - Brown, F.W., 1963 (Box 10)
    - Brown, G.M.L., 1937, 41 (Box 10)
    - Brown, G.W., Jr., n.d. (Box 10)
    - Brown, Howard E. C., 1961 (Box 10)
    - Brown, Hugh A., 1942 (Box 10)
      "Deluge of the Earth"
    - Brown, Nyal M., 1953 (Box 10)
    - Brown, Roger, 1961, 70 (Box 10)
    - Brown, Roland W., 1941, 56 (Box 10)
    - Brown, William L., Jr., 1958, 64 (Box 10)
      Pilot register in Zoology
    - Browning, G. Ossman, 1971 (Box 10)
    - Brozek, Josef, 1958, 61 (Box 10)
    - Bruce, Joan, 1971-72 (Box 10)
    - Bruce, Murray D., 1976 (Box 10)
    - Bruges Colloquium (Brugge), 1963-64 (Box 10)
    - Bruner, Jerome S., 1972 (Box 10)
    - Brusca, Richard C., 1975 (Box 10)
    - Bruzio, Arturo, 1934 (Box 10)
    - Bryan, Kirk, 1938, 46 (Box 10)
    - Bryden, William G., 1978 (Box 10)
    - Bryn Mawr College Science Club, 1950, 52 (Box 10)
    - Bryson, Vernon L., 1960 (Box 10)
    - Buchanan, J. William, 1935, 41, 45 (Box 10)
      Taxonomy/phylogeny of primates.
    - Buchanan, L.L., 1941 (Box 10)
    - Bucher, John, 1980 (Box 10)
      Punctuated equilibrium
    - Buck, Dan, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Buck, George S., Jr., 1964 (Box 10)
    - Buck, John, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Buckley, Walter, 1977 (Box 10)
    - Buddington, A.F., 1940, 47 (Box 10)
      APS nomination and comments
    - Budyke, M.I., 1979, 82-83 (Box 10)
    - Buenos Aires, Universidad, 1961, 1967 (Box 10)
      Candidates for professionship.
    - Buettner-Janusch, John, 1961-63, 65-67, 72, 74 (Box 10)
    - Bujak, B.J., 1937-38 (Box 11)
    - Bulletin of Atomic Scientists, 1960, 63, 64 (Box 11)
    - Bulman, O.M.B., 1929, 40 (Box 11)
    - Bumalda, John P., 1925-26 (Box 11)
      Paleontology at CA Inst Tech
    - Bump, James D., 1947 (Box 11)
    - Bunge, Mario, 1964, 77-79 (Box 11)
    - Bunge, William, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Bunker, Robert, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Burbank, W.S., 1953 (Box 11)
    - Burchsted, Fredric F., 1978 (Box 11)
    - Burdick, Clifford L., n.d. (Box 11)
    - Burdick, John M., 1962 (Box 11)
    - Bureau of American Ethnology, 1935, 41 (Box 11)
    - Burger, Alan, 1952 (Box 11)
    - Burges, Alan, 1950-51 (Box 11)
    - Burgess, Roy, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Burhoe, Ralph W., 1965 (Box 11)
    - Burke, Christopher E., 1977 (Box 11)
    - Burke, John J., 1933, 36, 39, 41-42 (Box 11)
    - Burkett, Sidney, 1970 (Box 11)
    - Burkhardt, Frederick, 1974, 76, 78 (Box 11)
      Darwin Correspondence Project
    - Burks, Verner I., 1963 (Box 11)
    - Burns, Ada K., 1942 (Box 11)
    - Burns, John M., 1976 (Box 11)
    - Burns, William A., 1978 (Box 11)
    - Buros, Oscar K., 1939 (Box 11)
    - Burpee, Lawrence J., 1941 (Box 11)
      fossil hunting in 1700s
    - Burrell, Harry, 1930 (Box 11)
      Platypus
    - Bursar's Office, American Museum of Natural History, 1939 (Box 11)
    - Burt, W.H., 1933 (Box 11)
    - Bush, Frank E., 1963 (Box 11)
    - Bush, Guy L., 1976 (Box 11)
    - Butler, E. Stanley, 1936 (Box 11)
    - Butler, Percy Milton, 1973-74 (Box 11)
    - Butterworth, Inc., 1965 (Box 11)
    - Butts, Bill, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Buwalda, J.P., 1932 (Box 11)
    - Buzzati-Traverso, Adriano and Baldi, Edgrado, 1948 (Box 11)
    - Byam, Nancy, 1961 (Box 11)
    - Bylinsky, Gene, 1979, 81 (Box 11)
    - Bynum, David, 1965 (Box 11)
    - Byrne, William P., 1973-74 (Box 11)
      Geography of Evolution
    - Caballero, Efren, Jr., 1941 (Box 11)
    - Cabe, Patrick A., 1974 (Box 11)
    - Cabral, Edward, 1980 (Box 11)
    - Cabrera, Angel, 1931-1954; 32.0 Item(s) (Box 11)
      Biographical and personal data; Genetics -- Horses; Museo de la Plata, Argentina; Paleontology; Publication -- Principles of Classification; Zoology
    - Cahalane, Victor H., 1959-60 (Box 11)
    - Cahn, Theophile, 1963 (Box 11)
    - Cailleux, A., 1953 (Box 11)
    - Cain, Arthur J., 1954-1982; 14.0 Item(s) (Box 11)
      Conferences and symposia; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Educational matters; Evolution; Leakey, Louis Seymour Bazett; Publication -- Animal Species and their Evolution; Requests for reprints; Teilhard de Chardin, Pierre; Zoology
    - Cain, Stanley A., 1948 (Box 11)
      Cranbrook Institute of Science, Michigan
    - Calaby, John, 1970-71, 78, 82 (Box 11)
    - Calgary, University of, 1971 (Box 11)
    - California Institute of Technology, 1925, 54 (Box 11)
    - California, University of (Box 11)
      - Berkeley, Museum of Paleontology, 1934-35, 65, 68 (Box 11)
      - Centennial Celebration, 1967-68 (Box 11)
      - Davis, 1968 (Box 11)
      - Hitchcock Professor Lecture, 1948-49 (Box 11)
      - Press, 1980 (Box 11)
      - San Francisco Medical Center, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Callahan, Joan R., 1979 (Box 11)
    - Callen, E.O., 1962 (Box 11)
    - Callison, George, 1976-77 (Box 11)
    - Calloway, N.O., 1966 (Box 11)
    - Camacaro, Juan J., 1969-71 (Box 11)
    - Camacho, Jorge Hernandez, 1959 (Box 11)
    - Cambray, F.W., 1976 (Box 11)
    - Cambridge University, 1965 (Box 11)
      Honorary degree
    - Cameron, W.J., 1941 (Box 11)
    - Camp, Charles L., 1939, 41-2, 45-50, 69-72 (Box 11)
    - Camp, Lee de, 1973 (Box 11)
    - Camp, Russell R., 1947 (Box 11)
    - Campa, Don Juan de la, 1930 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, Bernard, 1964-72 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, C.B.G., 1971, 75 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, C.K., 1976 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, Charles I., 1956 (Box 11)
      National Academy of Sciences
    - Campbell, David P., 1966-67 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, Donald T., 1963, 66-67 (Box 11)
      Evolutionary
      Epistimology
    - Campbell, Frank L., 1963 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, J.D., 1969, 71-72 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, K.S.W., 1972 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, Kenneth E., 1978-80 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, Paul A., 1964 (Box 11)
    - Campbell, Rod, 1969 (Box 11)
    - Campus World, Inc., 1959-60 (Box 11)
    - Canada, Department of Agriculture, 1966 (Box 12)
    - Canada, Public Archives of, 1941 (Box 12)
    - Canavan, John J., Jr., 1970 (Box 12)
    - Cane, Lee, 1976 (Box 12)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1960-61 (Box 12)
      "A Statement of Conviction/Overpopulation"
    - Canon U.S.A., 1973 (Box 12)
    - Canterbury Museum, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Cantore, Enrico, 1971-72 (Box 12)
    - Cantril, Hadley, 1947-51 (Box 12)
    - Cantwell, R.J., 1969, 82 (Box 12)
    - Capo de Lube, Josefina, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Cappelletti, Vincenzo, 1970-71, 75-76 (Box 12)
    - Caras, Roger A., 1964-65, 68 (Box 12)
    - Carbondale Public Schools (Colorado), 1925 (Box 12)
    - Carcasson, R.P., 1961 (Box 12)
    - Cardiac Pacemakers, Inc., 1977 (Box 12)
    - Cardon, Charlotte, 1983 (Box 12)
      Down House
    - Carey, Thomas J., 1974-75 (Box 12)
    - Carl Hanser Verlag, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Carleton University, 1966 (Box 12)
    - Carmichael, Leonard, 1958-59, 73 (Box 12)
      Smithsonian Institution
    - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1939, 42, 51 (Box 12)
    - Carneiro, Robert, 1955 (Box 12)
    - Carpenter, Frank M., 1958-59, 66-67 (Box 12)
      Committee on Evolutionary Biology, creationism
    - Carr, Paul, 1946 (Box 12)
    - Carr, William H., 1962-63, 77 (Box 12)
    - Carrelli, Antonio, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Carrington, Richard, 1963, 67, 69-71 (Box 12)
    - Carroll, Robert L., 1979-80, 83 (Box 12)
    - Carruth, Gorton, 1958 (Box 12)
    - Carter, Edward C., II, 1982 (Box 12)
      APS
    - Carter, G.S., 1954, 67 (Box 12)
    - Carter, John Pim, 1940 (Box 12)
    - Carter, Mr., 1927, 57 (Box 12)
    - Carter, R.T., 1982 (Box 12)
    - Carver, Kathleen, 1931 (Box 12)
    - Carworth, 1972 (Box 12)
    - Casamiquela, Rodolfo M., 1967-69, 73-74, 76-77 (Box 12)
    - Case, E.C., 1930, 34, 41 (Box 12)
    - Case, Lynn M., 1981 (Box 12)
    - Caspari, Ernst Wilhelm, 1956-1962; 6.0 Item(s) (Box 12)
      Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Evolution; Invitations; Recommendations
    - Castellanos, Alfredo, 1933-34, 38, 66 (Box 12)
    - Castellanos, Telasco R. Garcia, 1969, 73 (Box 12)
    - Caster, Kenneth E., 1942-43, 53 (Box 12)
    - Castetter, E.F., 1940 (Box 12)
    - Castiglioni, Franco, 1981 (Box 12)
    - Castri, Francesco di, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Cattell, J. McKeen, 1925-26, 35-36, 38 (Box 12)
    - Cattell, Jaques, 1943-45, 54 (Box 12)
    - Cattoi, Noemi, 1945-46, 60, 62-64 (Box 12)
    - Causey, David, 1964 (Box 12)
    - Cavalcanti, Tito, 1956 (Box 12)
    - Cayley, Hubert S., 1972 (Box 12)
    - Cazier, Mont. A., 1964 (Box 12)
    - Cellar Book Shop, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Cenozoic Research Laboratory, 1937 (Box 12)
    - Center for Advanced Study in Behavioral Sciences, 1956-58 (Box 12)
    - Center for Applied Linguistics, 1969 (Box 12)
    - Central High School (New York City), 1939 (Box 12)
      Transcripts for daughter
    - Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Cerqueira, Rui, 1975 (Box 12)
    - Cervenansky, W.E., 1963 (Box 12)
    - Chace, Jonathan, 1958 (Box 12)
    - Chachere, Marvin L., 1967, 1969-70 (Box 12)
      Centennial celebration at U. of California
    - Chadwick, George H., 1925-26, 35 (Box 12)
      Drometherium
    - Chaffee, Robert G., 1940, 42 (Box 12)
    - Chaline, Jean, 1981 (Box 12)
      "holobiologie"
    - Chamberlain, Will, 1960-61 (Box 12)
    - Chambers' Encyclopedia, 1946-47, 49-50, 60-61, 63, 65, 67 (Box 12)
    - Chambers, Bette, 1966, 76-77 (Box 12)
      Creationism and ACLU
    - Chamblee, Mildred, 1950 (Box 12)
    - Chaney, Dan, 1982 (Box 12)
    - Chaney, Ralph W., 1941, 48-50, 55-56, 66 (Box 12)
    - Chapin, James P., 1942 (Box 12)
    - Chapman, Frank M., 1932, 41 (Box 12)
    - Chapman, Frank M. (Memorial Committee), 1956-58 (Box 12)
    - Chapman, John W., 1938-39 (Box 12)
      Travel agent
    - Chaput, Linda, 1983 (Box 12)
    - Chardon, Carlos E., 1944 (Box 12)
    - Chargaff, Erwin, 1967 (Box 12)
    - Charig, Alan J., 1970, 72, 81 (Box 12)
    - Charreau, C., 1972-73 (Box 12)
    - Chase, Stuart, 1960 (Box 12)
    - Chastain, Murray (or Chastair), 1968 (Box 12)
    - Chatrath, Sarv Jit Singh, 1968-69 (Box 12)
    - Chatterjee, K.P., 1967 (Box 12)
    - Chatterjee, Sankar, 1973, 76 (Box 12)
    - Chaudhury, Buddha Deb, 1962 (Box 12)
    - Chayes, Felix, 1965 (Box 12)
    - Cheetham, Alan H., 1962 (Box 12)
    - Cheke, A.S., 1979 (Box 12)
    - Cherney, B.E., 1974 (Box 12)
    - Cherubin, Charles E., 1961 (Box 12)
    - Cheshire, Brian, 1981 (Box 12)
    - Chesnut, D. Lee, 1970 (Box 12)
    - Chicago, University of, 1934 (Box 13)
    - Chicago, University of (Darwin Centennial Celebration), 1957-60 (Box 13)
    - Chicago, University of (Press), 1947, 55-59, 64-65, 67, 77, 80-82 (Box 13)
    - Chick Publications, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Chickering, A.M., 1961 (Box 13)
    - Childs, George H., 1942 (Box 13)
    - Chilton Book Co., 1964-72 (Box 13)
    - China Institute in America, 1936 (Box 13)
    - China, Consulate General of the Republic of, 1935-36 (Box 13)
    - Chiquoine, Duncan, 1956 (Box 13)
    - Cholmeley, Jane, 1972-74 (Box 13)
      Yale University Press
    - Chorn, John, 1976 (Box 13)
      nomen vanum
    - Chow, Minchen, 1979-82 (Box 13)
    - Chowdhury, K.A., 1959 (Box 13)
    - Christen, Yves, 1977 (Box 13)
    - Christian Century (magazine), 1965 (Box 13)
    - Christian, John J., 1969 (Box 13)
    - Christodoulidis, P., 1978 (Box 13)
    - Chrulew, Stephen, 1969 (Box 13)
    - Church, F.S., 1965 (Box 13)
      Society for the Prevention of Missionaries
    - Church, Forrest E., 1962-63 (Box 13)
    - Church, Peggy Pond, 1965 (Box 13)
    - Chute, Robert, 1968 (Box 13)
    - Cifelli, Richard L., 1980-84 (Box 13)
    - Cigar Stores Realty Holdings, Inc., 1929 (Box 13)
      Stocks held by GGS
    - Cingolani, Carlos A., 1977 (Box 13)
    - Ciochon, Russell L., 1980 (Box 13)
    - Cione, Licenciado Luis Alberto, 1981 (Box 13)
    - Cirker, Hayward, 1962 (Box 13)
    - City College (New York City), 1957, 65-66 (Box 13)
    - Clark and Reid Company, 1959 (Box 13)
    - Clark, Agnes E., 1953 (Box 13)
    - Clark, Austin W., 1936 (Box 13)
    - Clark, Frank R., 1965 (Box 13)
    - Clark, James L., 1942 (Box 13)
    - Clark, John, 1936-37, 56-57, 59-61 (Box 13)
    - Clark, Kenneth W. (Mrs.), 1963 (Box 13)
    - Clark, L.W., 1950 (Box 13)
    - Clark, Robert D., 1972 (Box 13)
      Paleontology at U. of Oregon
    - Clark, T.H., 1943 (Box 13)
    - Clark, Wilfred E. LeGros, 1927-1970; 2 folders (Box 13)
      Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- Royal Society (Great Britain); Evolution; Honors; Human evolution, physical anthropology; Invitations; Leakey, Louis Seymour Bazett; Oxford University; Political issues -- England; Recommendations; Requests for reprints; Travel -- South America; World War II -- Impact on science; Zoology; Zoology -- Classification
      - Folder 1, 1927-1950 (Box 13)
      - Folder 2, 1951-1970 (Box 13)
    - Clark, Willard T., 1933 (Box 13)
    - Clarke, Harry M., 1979 (Box 13)
    - Clason, George S., 1951 (Box 13)
    - Clausen, Lucy W., 1953-54 (Box 13)
    - Cleaves, F.W., 1965 (Box 13)
    - Clegg, J.B., 1969, 76 (Box 13)
    - Clemens, Mildred, 1938 (Box 13)
    - Clemens, William A., 1959, 63, 67-68, 70, 73-74, 77-78, 80-83 (Box 13)
    - Clements, G.T., 1966 (Box 13)
    - Cleveland Bay Society of America, 1948 (Box 13)
    - Clewe, Thomas H., 1958 (Box 13)
    - Clinard, Elva H., 1982 (Box 13)
    - Clinton, H.G., 1941 (Box 13)
    - Cloak, F. Theodore, 1970 (Box 13)
    - Cloos, Ernst, 1952 (Box 13)
    - Clos, Helmut, 1960 (Box 13)
    - Cloud, Preston E., Jr., 1952-1979; 3 folders (Box 13)
      Conferences and symposia; Invitations; National Academy of Sciences; Paleontology; Publication; U.S. Geological Survey; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
      - Folder 1, 1952-1959 (Box 13)
      - Folder 2, 1965-1979 (Box 13)
      - Folder 3, 1966 (Box 13)
    - Clowes, William and Sons, Ltd., 1971 (Box 13)
    - Cobb, G.L., 1932, 35-36 (Box 14)
      Rail agent
    - Cobb, Stanley, 1960 (Box 14)
    - Coca Cola Co., 1971 (Box 14)
    - Cochran, Doris M., 1962 (Box 14)
    - Cockerell, T. D. A. (Theodore D. A.), 1933-1946; 16.0 Item(s) (Box 14)
      Insects in Patagonia
      Paleontology; Photographs; Publication; Zoology -- Insects
    - Coe, Michael D., 1969 (Box 14)
    - Coe, Robert, 1978 (Box 14)
    - Cohen, Morton, 1962 (Box 14)
    - Cohen, Robert S., 1965, 70 (Box 14)
      Boston Colloquim for the Philosophy of Science
    - Colbert, Edwin A., 1936-1980; 2 folders (Box 14)
      American Museum of Natural History; American Museum of Natural History -- Darwin exhibit; Biographical and personal data; Columbia University; Dunn, Leslie Clarence; Evolution; Paleontology; Publication; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Zoology
    - Colby College (Averill Lectures), 1950-51 (Box 14)
      Summary of Man's place in Nature
    - Cold Spring Harbor Symposium on Quantitative Biology, 1949-50, 58-59 (Box 14)
    - Cole, Kenneth, 1979 (Box 14)
    - Cole, Lois Dwight, 1936 (Box 14)
      MacMillan Co.
    - Cole, Thomas A., 1971 (Box 14)
    - Coleman, L.V., 1926 (Box 14)
    - Coleman, William, 1960, 64 (Box 14)
    - Coles, Charles, 1940 (Box 14)
    - Colgren, Charles, 1935 (Box 14)
    - Collard, Virgina, 1964 (Box 14)
    - College Entrance Examination Board, 1960-61 (Box 14)
      College Board and SATs
    - Collinge, Walter E., 1927 (Box 14)
      Amphilestes broderipii
    - Collins, R. Lee, 1941-42 (Box 14)
    - Collins, W.H., 1929 (Box 14)
    - Colloquium on Paleontology, Centre National de la Recherche Scientifique, Paris, 1946-48, 50 (Box 14)
    - Colorado Alumnus (newsletter), 1975 (Box 14)
    - Colorado College, 1960-61, 64 (Box 14)
      Summer conference for teachers
    - Colorado Geological Survey, 1972 (Box 14)
    - Colorado Seminary, 1967-68 (Box 14)
    - Colorado, University of, 1925, 53-54, 68 (Box 14)
    - Colorado, University of (Museum), 1963 (Box 14)
    - Colp, Ralph, Jr., 1966, 77 (Box 14)
      Darwin
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, 1946, 53 (Box 14)
    - Columbia Features, Inc., 1966 (Box 14)
      Under Twenty magazine
    - Columbia University, 1936, 1945-1959, 1961 (Box 14)
    - Columbia University (Conference on the Unity of Knowledge), 1953-1954 (Box 15)
    - Columbia University (Institute for the Study of the Biological Basis of Human Evolution), 1952-1953 (Box 15)
    - Columbia University (Jesup Lecture), 1959-60 (Box 15)
    - Columbia University (Latin Department), 1937 (Box 15)
    - Columbia University Press, 1961, 63, 65, 67-68, 78, 80-81 (Box 15)
    - Columbia University Press (Principles of Animal Taxonomy), 1960-61, 65 (Box 15)
    - Columbia University Press (Tempo and Mode in Evolution, 1st ed.), 1943-50 (Box 15)
    - Columbia University Press (Tempo and Mode in Evolution, 2nd ed.), 1950-56 (Box 15)
    - Columbia University Press (Tempo and Mode in Evolution, miscellany), 1944-51, 57 (Box 15)
    - Colwell, Rita R., 1975 (Box 15)
    - Combes, Lucien, 1981-82 (Box 15)
    - Comings, David E., 1965 (Box 15)
    - Commission on Undergraduate Education in the Biological Sciences, 1967-68 (Box 15)
      Conference on Explanation in Biology
    - Committee for Nuclear Information, 1966 (Box 15)
      Science and Citizen (bulletin)
    - Committee for World Development and World Disarmament, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Committee on Geological Names (USGS), 1936 (Box 15)
    - Committee on Scholarly, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Communication with the People's Republic of China Common Sense (magazine, South Africa), 1951 (Box 15)
      Review of Meaning of Evolution
    - Commoner, Barry, 1961-63 (Box 15)
      Biology curriculum
    - Community Church of New York, 1958 (Box 15)
    - Compton, F.E., Co., 1971-72 (Box 15)
    - Compton, Robert R., 1975-76 (Box 15)
    - Computer Devises and Terminal General, 1973-74 (Box 15)
    - Conant, Roger, 1941 (Box 15)
    - Concilium Bibliographicum (encyclopedia), 1926 (Box 15)
    - Conde, Jose Alverez, 1957 (Box 15)
    - Cone, William, 1961 (Box 15)
    - Conference Board of Associated Research Councils, 1952 (Box 15)
    - Conklin, Harold C., 1960, 64 (Box 15)
    - Conn, George H., 1951, 61 (Box 15)
    - Connecticut, University of, 1965 (Box 15)
    - Conners, Ed., 1954 (Box 15)